<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ataberk URAN</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ataberk URAN</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 06:00:23 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Duel It Yourself</title>
      <link>/posts/corrupted/corrupted/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 06:00:23 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/corrupted/corrupted/</guid>
      <description>DUEL IT YOURSELF Game made for the Global Game Jam 2020. It is a two-player westen duel in space. Rebuild your weapon quickly, aim and fire. Be careful about the gravity, and if you miss, you have to repair your gun all over again. First player to hit the other player 3 times wins.
I have worked with a group throughout the Global Game Jam 2020. During the Global Game Jam, I came up with the concept of the game according to the theme which was &amp;ldquo;Repair&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Duel It Yourself</title>
      <link>/posts/duel-it-yourself/duel-it-yourself/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 06:00:23 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/duel-it-yourself/duel-it-yourself/</guid>
      <description>DUEL IT YOURSELF Game made for the Global Game Jam 2020. It is a two-player westen duel in space. Rebuild your weapon quickly, aim and fire. Be careful about the gravity, and if you miss, you have to repair your gun all over again. First player to hit the other player 3 times wins.
I have worked with a group throughout the Global Game Jam 2020. During the Global Game Jam, I came up with the concept of the game according to the theme which was &amp;ldquo;Repair&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hypermasculine Unicorns of Anarchy</title>
      <link>/posts/unicorns/unicorns/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 06:00:23 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/unicorns/unicorns/</guid>
      <description>Hypermasculine Unicorns of Anarchy Game made for Indies vs PewDiePie Game Jam in 2014. In the game you are playing with Slick the Unicorn. All the unicorns have been kidnaped by the evil church and the main character Slick is trying to save his friends from them. Slick teams up with the badass motorcycle gang that can harness the power from the magical unicorns and become so much more powerful. With the help of the cyclists, Slick is ready to save his friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shadow That Pervades</title>
      <link>/posts/shadow-that-pervades/shadow-that-pervades/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 06:00:23 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/shadow-that-pervades/shadow-that-pervades/</guid>
      <description>DePaul Originals Game Studio   Our tasks specifically for this quarter was to completely overhaul and redesign a new more compact city space. At the beginning of the quarter, well thought it was important to establish some idea of deadlines for where we as a team would want to be throughout the quarter. It also helped because we wanted to make sure the ideas for the new space were in scope as it appeared last quarter the city level was a bit too large to allow for an immersive experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shoot House</title>
      <link>/posts/shoot-house/shoot-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 06:00:23 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/shoot-house/shoot-house/</guid>
      <description>Shoot House   A bulk of this team graduated in 2020 amidst the Corona Virus pandemic and in the middle of quarantine. As a result, many of us were caught in a vicious market with little guidance on how to proceed forward. That was until Vandalia Range and Armory approached our game design professor with a proposition. They wanted to hire a team of developers to create better games for their range.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
